SHINJUKU POLICE STATION
(新宿警察局)
Riddle Riddle, the Grocer,
“謎語人” “雜貨殿”
the Poisoner, Donner Donner,
“誕毒犯” “捐獻者”
and the Phantom Solitaire.
以及“怪人雪天鴉”
As you all know, these guys were either arrested
如各位所知 這些傢伙不是被逮捕
or confirmed dead.
就是已經確認死亡
Who came up with these strange names?
這些奇怪的名字都是誰起的啊
It was the leader.
是係長
You two! Keep quiet!
你們兩個 給我保持安靜
The names don't matter anyway.
名字什麼的怎樣都好啦
They won't be made public.
反正又不會公佈給大眾
So he cares that much.
原來他這麼介意啊
In short, we cannot disclose these guys to the public.
總之 我們無法把這幫傢伙公之於眾
Even if we do,
不 應該說即便我們公開
the public won't believe it. As for how to deal with them,
大眾也不會相信他們的存在 至於該如何對付他們
it's up to our "Comps-3",
就是我們“三輯”
that is Materials Compiling Group #3.
也就是“第三資料編輯係”的工作了
Also, there are Grim Reaper and Fire-breathing Bug,
另外“死神” “赴火之蟲”
as well as the Lemmings.
還有“旅鼠軍團”
Currently, these three calamities are still at large.
目前這三個災厄依然逍遙法外
Also, the bones were found at the scene of fire two days ago
不僅如此 還有前天 出現在火災現場的骨頭
and human bodies tied up were discovered yesterday.
以及昨天發現的打結的人體
We also found a footprint at the scene of human bodies tied up.
另外 我們在“打結”案件的現場 還發現了一個腳印
The footprint matches that of the Lemmings.
該腳印與“旅鼠軍團”的相吻合
And, the bones found
而且
at the scene of fire resemble ones of the Fire-breathing Bug case.
這次在火災現場出現的骨頭 和“赴火之蟲”一案十分相似
But we are not sure if it is related to human bodies tied up.
但我們目前還不確定 這些骨頭是否與打結的人體有關
In such a short time, two calamity-related clues appeared simultaneously.
但在如此短的時間內 同時出現兩個與災厄有關的線索
We cannot sit idly by.
我們無法坐視不管
Was that bone image synthesized?
那些骨頭是合成出來的影像嗎
After analyzing several videos,
我們分析過幾個影片後
we did not find any inconsistencies in the angle or size of the bones.
並未發現骨頭的角度和大小存在矛盾
If the bones in the video were synthesized in real-time,
如果影片裡的骨頭是即時合成的
then those videos cannot be used as evidence.
那些影片也就沒法當作證據了
Report complete.
我的報告到此結束
If it's an illusion,
如果那些骨頭是幻覺的話
then the explanation given by those children saved doesn't match.
就和那些得救的孩子們 給出的解釋對不上了
Netizens on Social media platforms and websites about supernatural phenomena
社交平台和討論超自然現象的網站上
are now in a heated discussion.
如今正鬧得沸沸揚揚呢
Alright, calm down.
好了 你們先冷靜
We've given reasonable explanations for all the calamities we encountered.
迄今為止遇到過的那些災厄 我們最後都給出了合理的解釋
Even the identity of Phantom Solitaire has been revealed
就連“怪人雪天鴉”
with the help of advanced technology.
我們也借助超前的極致技術 探明了他的真身
In the cases we have been responsible for,
由我們負責的案件中
In the future, it will only be the same.
今後也只會是這種情況
There must be humans behind these events.
這些事件的背後必定有人類在作祟
As long as these events are caused by the human,
只要對方是人類
we can handle it.
我們就有辦法能處理
(Dead Mount, Death Play)
《屍體如山的死亡遊戲》
Okay, the transfer has been successful.
好了 轉移成功
I have transferred the original soul
我已經將波爾卡原本的靈魂
of Polka into this doll.
轉移到這個玩偶裡面了
The drone can be returned to you now.
所以 無人機可以還給你了
Welcome back, my lovely drone.
歡迎回來 我可愛的無人機
I miss you so much.
我好想你啊
To be precise,
準確來說
Sorry about that.
抱歉
I still need to use your name and registration for a while.
我還要暫借你的名字和戶籍用一用
I won't use it for bad things.
我不會拿去做壞事的
What is this? So cute!
這是什麼 好可愛
Did Polka buy it?
是波爾卡你買回來的嗎
Wow, it turned so red.
哇 變得好紅喔
He can still get excited even when facing the woman who killed him.
即便是面對殺死自己的女人 這傢伙也能興奮起來嗎
Was Polka originally a strange kid?
難道波爾卡 原本就是個奇怪的孩子嗎
I simply can't understand what you're saying.
我根本聽不懂你在說什麼
I can make it speak normally
我可以讓它正常說話喔
as long as there is a fresh human vocal cord.
只要有新鮮的人類聲帶就行了
That's too difficult!
這難度也太高了吧
If we start from scratch,
從頭開始製作聲帶的話
it will consume a lot of magic power.
實在是太耗費魔力了
Currently, perhaps I should focus on replenishing my magic power
目前比起賺錢
rather than making money.
或許我更應該先補充魔力才對
However,
可是
the mana content in the atmosphere of this world is so low
這邊的世界 不僅大氣中的靈力含量稀薄
that it's almost impossible to sense the presence of elves.
而且也幾乎察覺不到精靈的氣息
How can you replenish magic power?
那你們要怎麼樣才能補充魔力啊
Usually, as long as there is a soul, magic power can be replenished.
正常來說 只要有靈魂的話我們就能補充魔力了
For the deceased to stay in the real world,
已逝之人要想留在現實世界中
it requires more energy than you can imagine,
其所需要的能量超乎你的想像
involving emotions such as hatred or attachment.
他們需要仇恨或是留戀之類的情感 才能製造能量
As necromancers,
而我們死靈術士
we are able to convert these emotions
能夠通過除靈
into magic through exorcism.
將這些能量轉換為魔力
So this building
因此這棟大樓
has accumulated more powerful magic compared with ancient battlefield.
所積攢的魔力 比古老的戰場還要濃厚得多
However, there aren't many places
可是類似這棟大樓的地方
like this building.
可沒有多少喔
It's okay,
沒關係
because there are also magic retention stones in this world.
因為這邊的世界也有魔留石
Mageez litension ston?
抹流時？
Here, magic stones are called gems,
用這邊的說法來說的話 就是被稱為寶石的那些石頭
such as diamonds or sapphires.
例如鑽石或者藍寶石之類的
In my world, they are high-density magic retention stones.
在我那邊的世界就是高密度的魔留石
If I had a bucket full of these magic retention stones,
如果可以有滿滿一桶這樣的魔留石
I could cast spells
然後再施展魔法的話
and make a fortune here.
我就可以在這裡大賺特賺了
Impressive.
這樣啊 那你蠻厲害的嘛
Come with me and experience the reality for yourself.
我就帶你去稍微領略一下現實吧
Such a small piece of stone
這 這麼一小塊石頭
costs the monthly salary of a police officer in this country?
就要價這個國家的警察一個月的工資
I didn't expect the price to be so high.
我沒想到價格居然這麼高
In your original world, are these gems cheap?
在你原本的世界裡 這些寶石很便宜嗎
Even children can buy them.
(帝國絢爛隊守護您的生活！) 這種東西連小孩子都可以隨便買
THE IMPERIAL GORGEOUS UNIT GUARDS YOUR LIFE! CREATING CONVENIENT LIVING WITH MAGIC CIRCUITS! HARVEST LARGE AMOUNTS OF MAGIC RETENTION STONES FROM MAGICAL CAVES!
(用魔力迴路打造便捷生活！) (從充滿魔力的洞窟中收穫大量魔留石！)
But in order to have a stable life,
但為了得到安穩的生活
I will not give up.
我是不會放棄的
I will save enough money
我要存到足夠的錢
and one day I will buy all the gems
然後總有一天我要將這家店裡的寶石
in this store at once.
全部一口氣買下來
PUT THE CART BEFORE THE HORSE
(本末倒置)
According to market price in the afternoon today,
根據本日下午的市價來計算的話
a total of 3.8127958 billion yen is needed.
您總共需要 38億1279萬5800日圓
I have no idea about the value of this country's currency,
因為我不知道這個國家貨幣的價值
Have a nice day.
本店十分感謝兩位的光臨
I clearly sensed a strong magic from the stone.
我明明從石頭裡感知到強大的魔力了 結果我卻什麼都沒辦法做
Can't you directly absorb the magic through the cabinet?
你不能透過櫃子 直接吸收石頭裡面的魔力嗎
If I do so, the stone will break
如果我那麼做的話 石頭就會碎掉
and it will be unfair to the people in the store.
這樣會很對不起店裡的人
You seem to behave yourself in such circumstances.
你在這方面倒是挺守規矩的嘛
So what should we do next?
那麼 接下來我們該怎麼做呢
Oh no!
糟糕
How indifferent.
真是冷淡啊
I didn't allow you to escape, criminal.
我可沒允許你逃啊 犯罪分子
Today I finally met you, Clarissa.
我今天總算是見到妳了 克拉麗莎
Policeman, what can I do for you?
警察先生 你找我有什麼事嗎
It's nothing. I just have a lot to say to you.
沒什麼 我只是有很多話想和妳說
Around the time when the fire broke out in Shakuzawa Building,
在酌澤大樓起火的那段時間前後
you seemed quite panicked.
你們的舉動貌似很慌張啊
Moreover, someone witnessed the drone
而且有人在那棟大樓的周圍
of that intelligence dealer around the building.
目擊到了那名情報販子的無人機
Besides,
除此之外
we also discovered a group of severely injured guys yesterday.
我們昨天還發現了一幫受重傷的傢伙
The leader of those people is a bastard
那些人的主腦是妳一手培養的
named Jimba who was cultivated by you.
名叫陣場的混蛋
I think there is some connection
我認為這其中存在著某種關聯
As a police officer,
作為警察
even if it's something difficult to inquire about, I still have to ask.
就算是不好打聽的事情 我也必須開口打聽才行啊
How much involvement does your organization have in these cases?
這些案件 到底和妳的組織有多大的關係
Lisa Kuraki.
倉木麗莎
Sorry, sorry.
抱歉抱歉
Did I scare you?
嚇到你們了吧
Please don't mind.
請別介意我剛才的舉動
Please.
拜託你們了
Okay.
好 好的
Be careful, Polka.
小心點 波爾卡
This guy is probably not easy to deal with.
這傢伙估計不好對付
Can you hear me, Takumi Kuruya?
你聽得到吧 繰屋匠
You can communicate
你的無人機
as long as the propellers
只要讓螺旋槳停下來就能進行通話 對吧
This troublesome guy caught me.
被這個麻煩的傢伙給逮到了
What should I do?
怎麼辦
Polka and Misaki haven't been targeted yet.
既然波爾卡他們還沒被盯上
Should I continue to remain silent?
我要不要乾脆一直保持沉默下去呢
Well…
那個
I should have asked you
我應該拜託過你們
not to interfere.
叫你們別多管閒事吧
Yes.
是的
But that drone
可是那架無人機
is very important to my friend.
是我朋友的很重要的東西
Friend? Did you mean Kuruya?
朋友 你是說匠嗎
Yes.
對
This is not good.
你這樣可不行啊
You should still be a high school student, right?
你應該還是高中生吧
If you hang out with that kind of bastard,
跟那種人渣混蛋待在一起
you will become one of them.
連你也會變成人渣的
Break off ties with him now.
你現在馬上跟他絕交吧
What's going on?
怎麼回事
His body is so cold.
他的身體好涼
What is bastard?
什麼是人渣 什麼是垃圾
What is filthiness?
什麼是污穢
I think it's society that
雖然我認為這些 是根據社會環境所決定的
but
但是
it's my freedom to choose who to be friends with.
要和誰做朋友是我的自由
Oh, I see.
這樣啊
I am starting to become interested in you.
我開始對你感興趣了
Can you tell me
你可以和我說說
about your situation?
你們的情況嗎
Kozaburo Arase.
荒瀨耿三郎
Although he is a police officer belonging to
雖說他是隸屬於
the Shinjuku police's Community Safety Division,
新宿警察局生活安全科的警察
he is a more dangerous guy than the thugs on the street.
但他卻是個 比街上的流氓更危險的傢伙
I used to be an intelligence dealer for the gang Sons of the Styx,
我曾經做過愚連隊的情報販子
and he killed eight members
而他當時當著我的面
of the gang in front of me in an instant,
讓武鬥派的八名成員
with blood splattering everywhere.
在一瞬間血濺當場
Can you hear me, Polka?
你能聽到我說話嗎 波爾卡
Ignore him.
不要回應我
That guy is very sensitive.
那傢伙的感覺很敏銳
You need to hide your own strength.
你得把自己的力量藏起來才行
If he targets you,
要是被他給盯上了
you won't have the peaceful life you wished for anymore.
你就別想過什麼安穩的生活了
That guy is a police officer.
那傢伙可是警官
Did he say that to you?
他是這樣和你說的嗎
He wanted to become friends with you.
說他要和你當朋友
People who casually talked about friendship like this
這種將友情隨便掛在嘴邊的傢伙
are actually suspicious.
反倒是最可疑的
Didn't your family teach you about this?
你家裡的人難道沒有教過你這種事嗎
I was sold by my parents,
我是被父母給賣掉的
so I don't understand what you mean by that.
所以我不懂你的意思
Sold?
被父母給賣掉？
Sorry, that happened in my past life.
抱歉 我忘記 那是前世的我經歷的事了
I'm becoming more and more interested in you.
我對你越來越感興趣了
Please tell me your name.
請你們務必告訴我你們的名字
Misaki has been going in and out of Clarissa's store
美咲在克拉麗莎的店裡
too frequently.
出入過於頻繁了
Polka probably hasn't been walking around there any less either.
波爾卡應該也沒少在那邊走動
It wouldn't be good if they are caught.
要是被他們給查到可就不妙了
Hey, Bro Arase,
嗨 荒瀨老哥
we haven't had a direct conversation in a long time, have we?
我們很久沒有直接交談過了吧
I'm really surprised that
真令人吃驚
you know my phone number.
你居然知道我的電話號碼
It seems like your skills have improved a lot compared to back then.
看來跟那時相比 你的技術長進了不少啊
Those two people are just playing games with me,
那兩個人只是陪著我一起玩遊戲的
they are family members of employees from Clarissa's place.
是克拉麗莎那裡的職員家屬
Both of them are innocent.
兩個人都是白紙一張
Can you spare them?
可以請你放過他們嗎
I conducted the interrogation just to verify if they were innocent.
我就是為了判斷這件事是否屬實 所以才會進行盤問的
I accept punishment for violating aviation regulations.
我知道自己觸犯了飛行條例 我甘願受罰
Isn't this better than
但我這樣總比 把你無端盤問普通人的影片
posting the video of you interrogating innocent people online?
給上傳到網路上還要好吧
Not bad. Are you trying to make a deal with me?
不錯嘛 你這是想和我做交易嗎
You're being so tough
你仗著我現在不在你面前
just because I'm not in front of you now.
就對我這麼強硬啊
You don't seem like the same person who betrayed friends before.
你現在真不像過去那個 出賣過自己同伴的你啊
At that time, you were crying and saying,
當時你一邊哭著一邊對我說
"I will provide information, so please don't hit me."
“我會提供情報給你的 所以請你不要打我”
Hey, do you really know
喂 你真的知道 繰屋匠是怎樣的一個人嗎
He is a guy who can easily betray his friends
他可是一個為了自保
for self-protection.
輕易就能出賣朋友的傢伙
He even told me things I didn't asked about,
甚至連朋友的妹妹身上有幾顆痣
like how many moles his friend's sister has.
這種我沒問過的事都會主動告訴我
How could I possibly know about that?
我怎麼可能知道那種事啊
That is a criminal lacking backbone.
那傢伙是個沒骨氣的犯罪分子
Did you know what he said behind your back?
他背地裡曾說過什麼
As long as one spends money,
只要花點錢
he will easily reveal your secrets to others.
他就會輕而易舉地 把你的秘密透漏給別人
My secret?
大嘴巴嗎
But at least
可是
he is better than you now.
他至少比現在的你要好
This guy
這傢伙
is definitely not an ordinary kid.
果然不是普通的小鬼
The heavy momentum is like a cannonball.
這份厚重的氣勢 簡直就像炮彈一樣
It's more like the underworld boss lurking in the Shura field?
不 應該說他更像是蟄伏在 修羅場當中的黑社會老大
An experienced soldier? Impossible.
還是說他是身經百戰的軍人 不對 這應該不可能
I don't want him to witness my power
我不想讓他見識到我的力量
or investigate my identity.
也不想讓他追究我的身分
What will Misaki do?
美咲她會怎麼做呢
Huh?
奇怪
Where did the girl who was with him go?
跟他在一起的那個女孩跑到哪去了
It's so scary.
好可怕好可怕
I almost got hit by this suspicious guy just now,
我剛剛差點被可疑的傢伙給打到了
Okay, let's escape quickly.
好了 我們快逃吧
If we stay here any longer, we will be attacked by him.
我們要是繼續留在這裡 可是會被他給襲擊的
The power she just displayed is not what a little kid should have.
剛剛那下 可不是小鬼頭應該有的力量
Where did they run off to?
他們跑到哪裡去了
It was really close.
真是千鈞一髮啊
Honestly, you are a big help.
老實說 妳幫了大忙
Kuruya
匠匠他
also messaged me, and told me
也給我發消息了
he is a police and let us escape.
他說“對方是警察 快逃”
Are you alright, Polka?
你沒事吧 波爾卡
Yes.
嗯 我沒事
Well…
那個
You have concerned about me,
雖然你講話有顧慮到我
and I am very happy.
我是很開心沒錯
But what you just said really overestimates me.
但剛才那番話 你實在是太抬舉我了
That guy didn't say it wrong,
那傢伙沒說錯
I value my own life very much.
我的確很看重自己的小命
If I were threatened,
如果我受到威脅的話 我大概不會多想
I probably wouldn't hesitate to sell the information about you.
便會將你的情報賣出去
You are overestimating me by saying that.
你這樣說才是高估我了
For me, there is no secret more important than
對我來說 沒有比朋友的性命
the lives of my friends.
更加重要的秘密了
May I ask,
我說啊
were you also that decisive in your past life?
前世的你做事也是這麼果斷的嗎
I mentioned the Geldwood Church to you before, right?
我之前跟你們提到過 蓋爾德伍德教團 對吧
The group used a sacred spell
在那群人使用的神聖術中
that can force others to reveal secrets.
有個能夠強行讓他人吐露秘密的法術
So for me,
所以對我來說
selling information is not a big deal to me.
出賣情報與否並不是什麼大不了的事
Is that church really holy?
那個教團真是神聖的嗎
At least one person should be.
至少有一個人應該是神聖的
SHINJUKU POLICE STATION
(警視廳新宿警察局)
Hey, Miss Aikawa.
嗨 合川小姐
Although it may sound a bit strange,
雖然我這麼說有點奇怪
can you please investigate this footprint?
但是可以請妳 幫我調查一下這個腳印嗎
What is this? It's hilarious.
這是什麼啊 笑死我了
By the way, isn't this a woman's shoe print?
話說 這不是女士的腳印嗎
What are you up to?
你幹什麼去了啊
Arase, you need treatment.
荒瀨 快來治療
SHINJUKU POLICE STATION, 25 YEARS OF SERVICE, FUMIYO YAMADA You need to get treated quickly.
(新宿警察局 工齡25年 山田文代) 得趕緊治療才行
Don't move, and take off your clothes.
你別亂動 趕快把衣服脫掉
Wait, no…
我說 那個…
That footprint…
那個腳印
It probably doesn't need to be investigated.
我大概不需要調查
Huh?
妳說什麼
I just saw it earlier.
我剛剛才看到過那個腳印
This is a footprint left at the scene of human bodies tied up.
這是在人體打結的現場留下的腳印
It's the most important evidence, besides the traces of the lemmings.
是除了旅鼠軍團的痕跡以外 最重要的證據
Look at that.
你看那個
It's so scary.
真是怪嚇人的啊
If you need treatment, go to the room.
你要治療的話就到房間裡去
The one on your back scared everyone.
你背上的那個嚇到大家了
I'm lucky!
中獎了
It's been a long time
久違地來了個有搞頭的案子啊
since we had an interesting case like this.
感覺會很有意思
The Comps-3 is chaotic.
“三輯”的那幫人感覺亂哄哄的啊
It seems like they have found traces of the Lemmings.
他們貌似是 找到了“旅鼠軍團”的痕跡
That calamity?
你說的是那個災厄嗎
That guy probably appeared
那傢伙大概是
five years ago.
五年前出現的吧
Killing, guarding, transporting goods,
殺人 護衛 運貨 綁架
kidnapping, robbing, destroying evidence.
搶劫 消滅證據 他為了賺錢
He does any job to make money.
什麼工作都做
Rumor has it that he is called the Jack-of-all-trades who stops at nothing.
他還被號稱為 “無所不為的萬事屋”呢
I only met him once in person.
我只有跟他打過一次照面
That guy is undoubtedly a monster.
那傢伙是無庸置疑的怪物
The group of people who confronted him
和他對陣的一夥人
even used submachine guns,
甚至還用上了衝鋒槍
but he twisted their necks
而那傢伙卻頂著槍林彈雨
while enduring the rain of bullets
扭斷了所有人的脖子
without hiding
他既不躲也不避
or avoiding them.
而是直接沐浴在槍林彈雨之中
Although I really want to say that
雖然我很想說 要靠我們自己的力量來逮捕他
it is ultimately under the jurisdiction of the Comps-3.
但那畢竟是“三輯”的管轄範圍
We can only leave it to Iwanome and his team to handle.
所以也只能交給岩野目他們來處理了
Although Iwanome is a strange man
雖說岩野目是個 在公務員考試中落第的
who failed the civil service exam,
性格乖僻的男人
we can't be fooled by his slovenly attitude.
但別看他平日裡一副吊兒郎當的模樣
In fact, he is a very principled man.
其實岩野目他是個很有骨氣的男人
Then I said,
然後 我就說了
"Stop trying to be clever."
“切 淨耍些小聰明”
No way.
討厭啦
That's something only the person who has been framed would say.
你那不是被害人才會說的台詞嗎
So what is that person here for?
所以那個人究竟是來做什麼的
He must have come to ask questions
他應該是來問話的吧
because he couldn't get a search warrant
因為他沒申請到搜查令
and wanted to gather information first.
所以他只能先過來打聽下情報
Hey, Lisa Kuraki!
喂 倉木麗莎
Speak honestly!
妳最好給我老實交代喔
I knew you must have a connection
我知道你們跟災厄脫不了關係
Confess now.
給我趕快交代
The Lemmings or Fire-breathing Bug are not your subordinates.
我知道“旅鼠軍團”或“赴火之蟲” 不是妳的手下
But the Grim Reaper is your subordinate, right?
但“死神”是妳的手下 沒錯吧
Who's the Grim Reaper? Sounds scary.
死神是什麼 好可怕
Lame min? What a cute name.
呂術軍團 好可愛的名字
The Lemmings
“旅鼠軍團”這號人啊
is a pretty scary person.
是相當可怕的傢伙喔
I was really scared when I saw him
看到他突破 30名機動隊成員的包圍網時
break through the encirclement of 30 members of the Mobile Squad.
我真的是嚇壞了
Don't disclose this to the media.
你們不要把這件事捅給媒體唷
Should I speak out about it?
我要不要說出去呢
Are we just going to let him be?
我們就這麼放任他不管嗎
The Shinjuku Police Station never released this intelligence.
我記得那應該是 新宿警察局沒有公開過的情報吧
Anyway, it's mutual.
是啊 不過我們這樣也是彼此彼此吧
This store
這家店
is no longer just a simple bar.
早就不是單純的酒吧了
He also understood this and came to provoke us.
不過 他也是明白這點 所以才會過來挑釁的吧
Even moving bones appeared at the scene of the fire.
因為火災現場甚至出現了會動的骨頭
I faintly scent a new calamity.
所以我隱約嗅到了新災厄的氣味
It's so scary.
哇 好可怕
If he catches our weak point, it will be bad.
要是被他揪住小辮子可就糟了
We need to warn Polka
我們得警告波爾卡他們
to be extra careful.
要讓他們多加小心才行
Clarissa, we came to play.
克拉麗莎 我們過來玩了
Bad timing.
他們來得可真不是時候
Hey hey, miss over there,
喂喂 那邊的小姐
are you still underage?
你們應該還是未成年人吧
You can't come to this kind of place.
你們不能來這種地方喔
Don't worry about it. I plan on ordering milk to drink.
不勞你費心 我們本來就打算點牛奶來喝
Kids have been so mature these days.
現在的小孩子還真是會玩啊
Hey, you two.
喂 你們兩個
I'm treating you to some juice.
我請你們喝果汁
Can you tell me what's popular among young people
你們可以告訴我現在在年輕人當中
these days?
都流行些什麼東西嗎
SHINJUKU POLICE STATION It's Arase.
(警視廳新宿警察局) 荒瀨
Where are they going?
他們要去哪裡啊
This direction is…
這個方向是…
Could it be… It's so hot!
難道說…好燙
Water spilled out.
灑出來了
So dangerous.
好危險好危險
And then, Hagane said to him,
然後呢 小鋼就說
"You're always trying to be clever"!
“你這傢伙 淨耍小聰明”
That's something only someone who has been framed would say.
那是被害人才會說的台詞吧
Who is Hagane?
誰是小鋼啊
What's wrong
這杯果汁
with this juice?
是怎麼回是
Before becoming this supernatural being,
比我變成這種超自然的存在前
I've never had such delicious drink.
喝過的任何東西都要好喝
I really want the people
我真想讓廢礦中的人們
in the wasteland to taste it too.
也嘗嘗這個味道
Why did he cry?
他為什麼哭了
I don't know.
我也不知道耶
Hey Polka! Are you in the bar?
喂 波爾卡 你們在店裡嗎
Don't reply me.
你不用回答我沒關係
If you are there, leave immediately from the back door.
如果你們在店裡的話 立刻從後門離開
Can you please move aside?
可以請你們讓開嗎
I am a customer, at least for now.
我們起碼現在還是客人喔
Okay, let him come in.
好吧 放他進來
Besides, his friend is also here.
再說他朋友也在這裡
Hey! Arase, over here!
嘿 荒瀨 這邊這邊
The woman is as cunning as a fox.
母狐狸
I didn't expect you to really be with her.
沒想到你真的和她在一起
You're the bad guy who just hit me
你是剛才那個打我
and tried to push me down.
還試圖將我推倒的壞人
I didn't try to push you down.
我可沒有試圖將妳推倒喔
You're really terrible.
你真是太差勁了
Leader?
係長 你說什麼
Just kidding.
我開玩笑的啦
Can I ask you two
兩位 我們可以和你們打聽點事情嗎
You don't want to be charged
你們也不想背上
with obstructing official duties, do you?
妨礙公務的罪名吧
Stop trying to be clever.
淨耍些小聰明
It wasn't us.
這不是我們幹的
Polka, what should we do?
波爾卡 我們要怎麼辦
Should we just run away?
直接逃掉嗎
That seems like the best option.
那樣好像會比較好
I'll lead the way this time.
這次由我來帶路
That's a bold proposal.
這真是大膽的提議呢
Polka?
波爾卡？
What's going on? Who is here?
怎麼回事 有什麼人在這裡
Let me provide the light.
我點個火哦
Hey, is this for real?
喂喂 真的假的
Why are you here?
你為什麼會在這裡
Lemmings.
“旅鼠軍團”
(Episode 5: The Monster)
(第5集 The Monster -怪物-)